Trotiner, Glen M.; Papers mss154
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Biographical and Subject Files, 1969-2022
  - "The Mental State" Production Information [RESTRICTED], 2018 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "The Mental State" Script, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Motion Picture Legislation Research, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Negatives, 4 at Tommy's Party, #11, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Negatives, 20th Anniversary Party, 1975 December (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Negatives, Alice #18, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Negatives, Anita's Pictures [plus] WSUA, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Negatives, Billy Mumy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Negatives, Brigadoon, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Negatives, Bryce Zion Ground, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Negatives, Bryce, Grand Canyon (shirts), Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Negatives, Busboys, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Negatives, Calgary, Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Negatives, Camelot, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Negatives, "Can a beer", Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Negatives, Chicago Thanksgiving, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Negatives, Crater Lake, Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Negatives, Damn Yankees, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Negatives, Damn Yankees, Tommy + Car, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Negatives, Dave's 1st Surprise, Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Negatives, Dave + Chris Party- Montauk, 1977 February (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Negatives, Denver, 1980 July (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Negatives, Devil's Tower, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Negatives, Don Metzner [and] Joe Singer, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Negatives, Enterprise #5, Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Negatives, Fisherman's Wharf, Alcatraz, Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Negatives, Fisherman's Wharf, Muir Woods, Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Negatives, Florida, 1976 January (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Negatives, Florida- Mike + Larry, Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Negatives, Frisco, Alcatraz, 1980 July (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Negatives, Garden of the Gods, Iowa, 1980 July (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Negatives, Halloween, Undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Negatives, Houston, New Orleans, Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Negatives, Karate-3 in White Belts, Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Negatives, LA (castle) (cecil), Undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Negatives, Labor Day, Undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Negatives, Lombard, Undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Negatives, Midnight Supper, Undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Negatives, Mt. Rushmore -Night, Devil's Tower, Undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Negatives, New Years Eve, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Negatives, Outdoor Party, 1977 May (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Negatives, Party-Montauk, 1977 February (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Negatives, Pete's Country House, Undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Negatives, Pete's Party, Undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Negatives, Pinching Doc's Nose Disney #8, Undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Negatives, Roosevelt, Anything Goes, WPIX Mitch, Undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Negatives, Salt Lake, Tahoe, San Fran (cable car), Undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Negatives, San Antonio, Undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Negatives, Sugar, Undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Negatives, Suite, 1977 April (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Negatives, Theater-unlabeled, Undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Negatives, Tom [and] Pete [and] Glen-Florida, 1977 February (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Negatives, Tommy + Glen Castle #1, Undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Negative's Tommy's Surprise, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Negatives, Tom's Party, 1976 September (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Negatives, Trips, Undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Negatives, Twin Pines, Camelot, Undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Negatives, Twin Pines Summer, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Negatives, Universal, Universal- #4 Strangled by Frankenstein, Undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Negatives, Various- In and Around Suite, 1977 January (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Negatives, Wizard of Oz, Undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Negatives, Yellowstone, Undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - New York Film and Video Monitor Article About "Overnight Sensation" and Sundance Film Festival, 2001 March (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Notes on Schedule, Undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Off Broadway Contract with Right to Move It to Broadway, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Off-campus Student Teacher's Program for English, 1978; Undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Oneline Schedule, Unknown Film, 1988 November 14 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - "Pandora" Script, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - "Perfect Stranger" Rehearsal Notes, Communications, Production and Script Notes, 2002; 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Personal History and Biography, Undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Personal Photos, Undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Photo, Paul Revere Headstone/Monument, Undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Photos and Negatives, Dolly, 1980 April (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Photos and Negatives, Disneyland Night, San Diego Zoo, Undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Photos and Negatives, Family at Grandmas, Undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Photos and Negatives, Filming Photos, Undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Photos and Negatives, Florida, 1976 January (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Photos and Negatives, Granby, Undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Photos and Negative, Grand Canyon, 1980 August (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Photos and Negatives, Halloween Party, Undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Photos and Negatives, Hearst Castle, Undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Photos and Negatives, Hello Dolly, Undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Photos and Negatives, Hello Dolly Poster, 1980 April (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photos and Negatives, In and Around Suite, 1977 May (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photos and Negatives, Jackson Hole, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Photos and Negatives, Judy Diamond Party, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photos and Negatives, L.A., Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photos and Negatives, Lyndhurst, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photos and Negatives, Radisson, Mesa Verde, Boatride, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Photos and Negatives, Radio Show, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Photos and Negatives, Route 80-70-Clev-Chicago-Bloomington-St.Louis, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Photos and Negatives, Rushmore, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Photos and Negatives, Salt Lake, Tahoe, San Fran, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Photos and Negatives, San Francisco, Yosemite, Grandmans, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Photos and Negatives, Suite, 1977 March (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Photos and Negatives, Teen Travel Canada, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Photos and Negatives, Teen Travel Washington, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Photos and Negatives, Theater, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Photos and Negatives, Tom Sawyer Play, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Photos and Negatives, Trips, Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Photos and Negatives, Universal, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Photos and Negatives, Universal, Vegas, Bryce, 1980 July (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Photos and Negatives, Unknown, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Photos and Negatives, Unlabeled Family/Personal Photos, 1952; 1968; 1978; Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Photos, Black and White from Play of Glen Trotiner, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Photos, Florida-Glen, Tom, Pete, 1977 February (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Photos from Filming "Brighton Beach Memoirs", Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Photos from Filming "The Untouchables", Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Polaroids from Unknown Film, Funeral Scenes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Photos, Teen Tour, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Photos, Tommy's 1st Surprise, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Printed Online Articles, 2017-2018 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - "Professor Pasghetti" Script, Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - "Querido Tiempo "Wire Trip"" Creative Presentation, 2018 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - "Regarding Henry" Bound Script, 1990 September 11 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - "Regarding Henry" Production Information, 1980 October (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Research, Beatles Singles in Date Order, 2018 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Research Files, 1969-1983 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Research Files, Newspaper Articles, 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Research, Film School, 1980; Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Research, July 1969 News Items (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Research, Sunrise and Sunset at Tampa Florida, 1992 March 24 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Richard Gere Headshot, Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Robert Jencks and Incline Productions Branding Round 2 Presentation, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - "Say Hello to Dolly" Play at Northeast Jewish Center, 1980 April (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - School Photos, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Screen Actors Guild Minimum Free Lance Contracts, John Schuck Not Signed, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - "Second Sight" Authorization of Engagement of Artist, 1988 April (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - "Second Sight" Folder of Larimar Film Entertainment Communications Regarding Filming, 1988 March (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - "Second Sight" Production Information, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - "Second Sight" Shooting and Location Schedule and Production Information, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - "See No Evil, Hear No Evil" Photos by Michael Ginsburg (1 of 2), Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - "See No Evil, Hear No Evil" Photos by Michael Ginsburg (2 of 2), Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - "See No Evil, Hear No Evil" Time Plot, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - "Serenade" Production Information, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - "Serenade" Script, 2018 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "She Devil" Meryl Streep Headshot, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "She Devil" Negatives, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - "The Shuroo Process" Artist Confidential Deal Memos [RESTRICTED], 2018-2019; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Smitherens Script Page Changes, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Space Articles and Filming Science Fiction, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - "Spaceship Earth" Script Crankite Version, 1986-1994; 2005 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - "Squirt-TV", 1989; 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Staff and Crew Lists, Various Films, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Star Trek Set, Negatives, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Studio Comparison Spreadsheet, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Subject Files, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - The Superman Movie, Childhood Collection, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Time Out New York Magazine Articles, 2016-2017 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Thank You Cards From Professor Segal's Students, 2018; 2022; Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "Trolled" Script, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - UAlbany Magazine Article about Trotiner, 2017 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - UAlbany Radio Folders, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - UAlbany WSUA Radio Station, News Articles and Posters, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified Headshot, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Photos, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - "The Untouchables" Bound Script, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "The Untouchables" Bound Script with Revision History, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "The Untouchables" Film and Production Information, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "Untrue Blue" New York Magazine Article, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Court of Appeals, Film Allman vs. Secretary of Labor, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Various Unsigned Forms, 2014; 2016; Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Variety, "Brighton Beach Memoir" Mentioned Twice, 1985 September 11 (Oversize 1, Folder 1)
  - Variety, "Power" Mentioned Twice, 1985 April 10 (Oversize 1, Folder 2)
  - WSUA, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - "Zero Shapiro" Script, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)